Guide to the Edna St. Vincent Millay Papers, 1892-1988
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series IX: Photographs
  - Photographs of Millay's Youth (circa 1893-1914)
    - Snapshot at Whitehall Inn, 1912; (1 item) (Folder 14.8)
    - Snapshot at Great Spruce Head, 1913; (1 item) (Folder 14.9)
    - Snapshot at Warren Island, ME [ref. no. 6.205], 1914; (2 items) (Folder 14.10)
  - Photographs of Millay at Vassar (1914-1917)
    - Portrait by Arnold Genthe [ref. no. 3.71], 1914; (4 items) (Folder 14.11)
    - Snapshot at Vassar under porte-cochere [ref. no. 3.408], undated; (3 items) (Folder 14.12)
    - Portrait in Vassarion [ref. no. 6.211], 1917; (3 items) (Folder 14.13)
  - Millay Portraits (circa 1917-circa 1940, undated)
    - Portrait, circa 1917; (3 items) (Folder 15.1)
    - Portrait, [circa 1920s?]; (1 item) (Folder 15.2)
    - Portrait, [circa 1920s?]; (1 item) (Folder 15.3)
    - Millay and Eugen Boissevain [ref. no. 6.187], [1923]; (1 item) (Folder 15.4)
    - Portrait [ref. no. 6.188], 1923; (2 items) (Folder 15.5)
    - Portrait [ref. no. 6.191], 1923; (3 items) (Folder 15.6)
    - Snapshot of Millay and Eugen Boissevain on a boat, [circa 1924]; (1 item) (Folder 1.16)
    - Snapshot at Tuft's College, 1925; (2 items) (Folder 15.7)
    - Sacco and Vanzetti March, 1927; (1 item) (Folder 15.8)
    - Portrait [ref. no. 6.193], 1929; (3 items) (Folder 15.9)
    - Portrait [NBC], [circa 1930s?]; (1 item) (Folder 15.10)
    - Portrait, [circa 1930s?]; (1 item) (Folder 15.11)
    - Portrait, [circa 1930s?]; (3 items) (Folder 15.12)
    - Portrait, [circa 1930s?]; (3 items) (Folder 15.13)
    - Portrait, [circa 1930s?]; (1 items) (Folder 15.14)
    - Portrait, circa 1931; (2 items) (Folder 15.15)
    - Portrait [NBC] [ref. no. 6.206], circa 1934; (3 items) (Folder 16.1)
    - Portrait [NBC] [ref. no. 6.200], circa 1934; (2 items) (Folder 16.2)
    - Portrait [NBC], circa 1934; (2 items) (Folder 16.3)
    - Portrait [ref. no. 3.407], 1937; (3 items) (Folder 16.4)
    - Portrait [NBC] [ref. no. 6.169], circa 1940s; (1 item) (Folder 16.5)
    - Portrait, undated; (2 items) (Folder 16.6)
    - Snapshot, undated; (1 item) (Folder 16.7)
    - Matted framed Millay portrait, signed by Arnold Genthe, [1914]; (1 item) (Folder 21.3 (Oversize))
  - Other Images of Millay
    - Sketch of Millay by E.B. Kelley, undated; (2 items) (Folder 16.8)
    - Millay Portrait in Oil by M. Kopf, undated; (1 item) (Folder 16.8)
    - Millay bust by H.P. Erskine, undated; (2 items) (Folder 16.10)
  - Vassar College Productions
    - Vassar College Production — Sophomore Party, 1914; (1 item) (Folder 16.11)
    - Vassar College Production — Sophomore Party, 1914; (1 item) (Folder 16.12)
    - Vassar College Production — "Candida,", 1915; (1 item) (Folder 16.13)
    - Vassar College Production — "Candida,", 1915; (1 item) (Folder 16.14)
    - Vassar College Production — "Candida" [ref. no. 6.187], 1915; (2 items) (Folder 16.15)
    - Vassar College Production — "Pageant of Athena,", 1915; (1 item) (Folder 17.1)
    - Vassar College Production — "Pageant of Athena,", 1915; (1 item) (Folder 17.2)
    - Vassar College Production — "Pageant of Athena,", 1915; (4 items) (Folder 17.3)
    - Vassar College Production — "Pageant of Athena,", 1915; (2 items) (Folder 17.4)
    - Vassar College Production — "Deirdre of Sorrows,", 1916; (3 items) (Folder 17.5)
    - Vassar College Song Contest — "The Patient Periodical,", 1916; (8 items) (Folder 17.6)
    - Vassar College Production — "The Locked Chest,", 1916; (2 items) (Folder 17.7)
    - Vassar College Production — "Aria da Capo,", [1921]; (1 item) (Folder 17.8)
    - Vassar College Production — "The Lamp and the Bell,", 1921; (1 item) (Folder 17.9)
  - Productions of Works by Millay
    - ["Aria da Capo"?], undated; (1 item) (Folder 17.10)
  - Family Members
    - Boissevain, Eugen, (4 items) (Folder 18.1)
    - Millay, Cora Lounella Buzzelle, (4 items) (Folder 18.2)
    - Millay, Cora with Albert Parson, husband of Clementine Parsons, undated; (1 item) (Folder 18.3)
    - Millay, Henry Tolman, [circa 1892?]; (3 items) (Folder 18.4)
    - Parson, Clementine (Millay's "Auntie Kem", or "Aunt Clem"), (4 items) (Folder 18.5)
  - Millay Homes
    - Millay homes [includes ref. no. 6.212, 6.214], (11 items) (Folder 18.6)
  - Millay at Steepletop
    - Millay at Steepletop (NBC Photo?), [1942?]; (1 item) (Folder 18.7)
    - Millay at Steepletop (NBC Photo?) [ref. no. 6.203], [1942?]; (1 item) (Folder 18.8)
    - Millay at Steepletop (NBC Photo?), [1942?]; (1 item) (Folder 18.9)
    - Millay at Steepletop (NBC Photo?), [1942?]; (1 item) (Folder 18.10)
    - Millay at Steepletop (NBC Photo?) [ref. no. 6.202], 1942; (4 items) (Folder 18.11)
    - Millay at Steepletop, undated; (4 items) (Folder 19.1)
    - Millay at Steepletop, undated; (4 items) (Folder 19.2)
    - Millay at Steepletop, undated; (5 items) (Folder 19.3)
    - Millay at Steepletop, undated; (1 item) (Folder 19.4)
    - Millay and Boissevain at Steepletop, undated; (3 items) (Folder 19.5)
  - Steepletop
    - Steepletop's Bar [picture includes Margaret Cuthbert], undated; (1 item) (Folder 19.6)
    - "Last Photo of Edna and Eugen" at Steepletop [includes ref. no. 6.186], 1948; (6 items) (Folder 19.7)
    - Steepletop, 1958; (6 items) (Folder 19.8)
    - Steepletop, undated; (1 item) (Folder 19.9)
    - Steepletop's Kitchen [ref. no. 6.216], undated; (3 items) (Folder 19.10)
    - Steepletop's Kitchen, undated; (2 items) (Folder 19.11)
    - Steepletop's Kitchen, undated; (2 items) (Folder 20.1)
    - Steepletop's Kitchen, undated; (3 items) (Folder 20.2)
    - Steepletop's Kitchen, undated; (2 items) (Folder 20.3)
    - Steepletop's Kitchen, undated; (2 items) (Folder 20.4)
    - Steepletop's Kitchen, undated; (2 items) (Folder 20.5)
    - Steepletop's Kitchen, undated; (2 items) (Folder 20.6)
    - Steepletop's Kitchen, undated; (2 items) (Folder 20.7)
    - Steepletop's Kitchen [includes ref. no. 6.209, 6.210], undated; (3 items) (Folder 20.8)
    - Steepletop's Kitchen [includes ref. no. 6.207, 6.208], undated; (2 items) (Folder 20.9)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Austerlitz, NY, undated; (1 item) (Folder 20.10)
    - Camden, ME High School, undated; (1 item) (Folder 20.11)
- SERIES X: SCRAPBOOKS
  - Scrapbook of Walter Adolphe Roberts, undated; (1 item) (Box 22)
  - Scrapbook of Lilian R. Huguenin [contains some Millay letters], undated; (1 item) (Box 22)
  - Scrapbooks of Charlotte Babcock Sills, undated; (2 items) (Box 23 (Oversize))
- SERIES XI: REALIA
  - "Poets' Homesteads — Steepletop, Austerlitz, NY" Ceramic Tile, 1955; (1 item) (Folder 21.2 (Oversize))
  - Gorham 2 1/2 pint silver urn. Inscribed, "Margaret and Alice their Bread-and-Milk Bowl from Aunt Edna and Uncle Ugin,", (1 item) (Box 24)
  - Print Blocks from Vassar Alumnae Magazine article on Millay, Feb 1957 (Box 29)